isagaming.com 2006-12-05

# Privacy Policy - eHow.com

eHow knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting any of the sites offered by eHow, Inc., you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice. For question on the Privacy Notice please contact [legal@ehow.com](mailto:legal@ehow.com).

### – What Personal Information About Me Does eHow Gather?

  * #### Information You Give Us:

We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, providing our services, and communicating with you.
  * #### Automatic Information:

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our sites. Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) click stream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time. We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

### – What About Cookies?

  * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser.
  * Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

### – Does eHow Share the Information It Receives?

Yes, we do share information but only as described below. Otherwise we will not provide your personal information without your consent.

  * **Advertisers:** We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.
  * **Partners:** We partner with other parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services.
  * **Agents:** We engage other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include providing marketing assistance, providing customer services, sending postal mail and email to you, removing repetitive information from customer lists, and analyzing data. These persons have access to personal information needed to perform their functions. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information that you provide to eHow for any secondary purposes
  * **Service Providers:** We engage other companies and individuals to perform enhanced services on our behalf. In addition, certain of our enhanced services require that we contact Internet directories and various search engines on your behalf. Many of our service providers have access to personal information needed to perform their services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
  * **Business Transfer:** As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or their assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets.
  * **Compliance:** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of eHow, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

### – How Secure Is Information About Me?

  * We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input and the information we may send to our agents.
  * It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

### – Links

  * Sites provided by eHow contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

### – Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions

  * If you choose to visit eHow, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Washington. If you have any concern about privacy at eHow, please send us a thorough description to [legal@ehow.com](mailto:legal@ehow.com), and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Terms of Use will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.

Demand Media, eHow, and weHow are trademarks or registered trademarks of Demand Media, Inc. in the United States and/or other countries. 

Copyright © 2006. Demand Media, Inc.

Last updated: October 25, 2006
